theinfostrides.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy and Terms | The InfoStrides

**Our Privacy Policy & Terms of Service (TOS)** set out how **The InfoStrides** uses and protects any information that you give The InfoStrides when you use this website and the information provided to you on our website.

The InfoStrides is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. While not taking any legal responsibility for the information provided on our website, The InfoStrides ensures that the series ofinformation on our website are censored and moderated to the best of our knowledge.

The InfoStrides may change this  **Privacy Policy & Terms of Service (TOS)** from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 7th April, 2010.

### What We Collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Username
  * Contact information such as e-Mail Address, Messenger ID, and website
  * Demographic information such as age, gender, location and country
  * Other relevant information such as personalized picture, and date of birth.

### What We Do with the Information We Gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for vital information within the scope of the website. We may contact you by email or personal message (PM). We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Note about Advertising

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Disclaimer

The InfoStrides publishes information related to business, careers, education, entertainment & sports, free downloads, global news, jobs & vacancies, technology, travel & places, and many more. The series of information posted on The InfoStrides are personal contributions of their respective posters. Therefore, there is no obligation whatsoever with the posters, companies and the web administrators. Hence, are not liable for the correctness of the information.

More so, the users should be informed that The InfoStrides is not liable for any business whatsoever that occur as a result of using the information which was mainly compiled for the benefit of the members and visitors in Nigeria and abroad.

### Job and Recruitment Scams

This is a special warning for job seekers generally. They should bear it in mind that The InfoStrides is not liable or responsible for any recruitment or employment contracts undergo through jobs and careers related information posted on the website. The series of information provided are only meant to create awareness about opportunities around.

We do not in anyway expect members/visitors/candidates or job seekers to pay any form of money to apply for jobs, be short listed for interviews or attend training programs.

Please do not pay to any organization that claims to be The InfoStrides. We neither solicit nor request for money from job seekers.

Employers or agencies that ask for money, are fake and do not exist. They are scammers and fraudsters: none of these forms of requests originate from either our site or that of any of our affiliates. These sorts of scams may be a part of the notorious Advance Fee Fraud, popularly known as 419. Please beware and be careful!!!

**NB:**  If you were asked to pay through any of the information provided on our website, please [Contact Us](http://www.theinfostrides.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") or post it on the [forum](http://www.theinfostrides.com/forum/ "The InfoStrides Forum").

### Links To Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Controlling Your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by [writing](http://www.theinfostrides.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us") to or [emailing us](http://www.theinfostrides.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please [Contact Us](http://www.theinfostrides.com/contact-us/ "Contact Us").

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Updated: 27th November, 2013.
